Guide to the Partners for Livable Communities records, 1960-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 6: Shared Heritage of the Americas, 1982-1995; (5 boxes)
  - Spanish Legacies in the Built Environment, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Spanish Legacies in the Built Environment, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - The City and the River, 1985 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Toward 1992: Public Programs on Nautical Archaeology in the New World, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Underwater Archaeology, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Underwater Treasure Research, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Underwater Treasure Research, 1992 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Undiscovered Gifts of the Caribbean, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Undiscovered Gifts of the Caribbean, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 4)
- Series 7: Tourism: Heritage, Discovery, and Ecotourism, 1979-2008; (9 boxes)
  Series 7, Tourism: Heritage, Discovery, & Ecotourism, includes materials focused on the importance of conservation and tourism development.
  - African American Heritage Centers, 2004 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - African American Heritage Tourism and Community Development, 1999 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - African American Heritage Tourism and Community Development: A report to the United States Economic Development Administration, 2000 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - African American Heritage Tourism and Community Development: A report to the United States Economic Development Administration, 2000 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - African-American Museum of Delaware, 2000 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - African-American Museum of Delaware, 2000 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - African-American Museum of Delaware Board Retreat, 2000 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - African-American Museum of Delaware Charrette, 2000 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - African-American Museum of Delaware Charrette, 2000 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - African-American Museum of Delaware Charrette, 2000 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - African-American Museum of Delaware Charrette, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - African-American Museum of Delaware Charrette, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Black Heritage Tourism: Education or Exploitation?, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Black Heritage Tourism: Education or Exploitation?, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Black Heritage Tourism: Education or Exploitation?, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Brisbane: A Temporary Paradise? A Report on the Visit to Brisbane, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Chattanooga Venture, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Civic Tourism Comments, 2001 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Civic Tourism Information, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Collaborative Caribbean Preservation Strategy, 1984 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Community Development Combined With Cultural Heritage Tourism, 1998 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Community Development Combined With Cultural Heritage Tourism, 1998 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Community Development Combined With Cultural Heritage Tourism, 1998 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Community Development Combined With Cultural Heritage Tourism, 1998 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Conference Proceedings from the "Challenges and Choices for the 1990's", 1982 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Conservation and Tourism, 2000 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Conservation and Tourism, 2000 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Council of Foundations Annual Meeting Panel on Heritage Tourism, 2000 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Cultural Heritage Tourism: A Vehicle for Dynamic Social and Economic Change, 2008 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Cultural Tourism and Gritty City Enhancement Strategies: Appealing to the Landscape and of the Mind, 1997 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Cultural Tourism and Sustainable Development, 1981 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Cultural Tourism and Sustainable Development, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Cultural Tourism in America, 1986 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Cultural Tourism: A New Opportunity for the Industrial City?, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Cultural Tourism: A New Opportunity for the Industrial City?, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Cultural Tourism: Wedding Conservation to Economic Development, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Destination Where? Putting Cities Without Surf, Slopes, and Slot Machines on the Map, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Destination: Tourism Development, Indianapolis Maximized its Assets, 1984 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Developing Communities through Cultural, Heritage and Ecological Tourism, 1995 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Tourism: Understanding Resource Conflicts Bonaire, Netherlands Antilles, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Getting Into Brisbane: Focus on 90's, 1989 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - International Perspective on Cultural Parks, 1989 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Island Legacy: Protecting the Heritage of the Caribbean and the Bahamas, 1990 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Jackson Hole Community Center for the Arts, 1996 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Managing Cultural Resources for the Tourist, 1999 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Managing Tourism Growth: Issues and Applications, 2000 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - New Prospects for Cultural Tourism in America, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Partners for Livable Communities: A Case Study, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Partners: Conservation and Heritage Tourism, 1988 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Place Magazine: "Tunisia Granary of Rome", 1989 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Planning for Cultural Tourism, 1981 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Prospects for Regional Tourism Development in New England, 1983 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Putting the Arts to Work: An Action Plan for Cultural Tourism in Jackson Hole, Wyoming, 1980 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Reflections on Cultural Tourism and Transportation, 1980 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Responsible Tourism Debate, 1980 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Revitalizing Industrial Cities Through Cultural Tourism, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Sorrento Peninsula: Preserving Its Past, Planning Its Future, 1979 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Thoughts Concerning the Creation of a Local Tourism Development Plan, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Tourism and Caribbean Cultural Identity, 2003 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Tourism and Conservation, 1994 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Tourism and Cultural Conservation: Insuring Uniqueness of Place in the Developing World, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Tourism and New England Seaports: Conservation, Development, and Design, 1992 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Tourism and the Community: Changing Relationships, 1998 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Tourism and the Economic Development of the Older Industrial City, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Tourism and the Environment: Challenges and Choices for the 90's, 1997 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Tourism and Urban Regeneration, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Tourism Begins at Home, 1992 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Tourism Development and Cultural Conservation: Ways to Coordinate Heritage with Economic Development, 1981 (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - Tourism Development in America has been Sorely Neglected as a Tool for Economic Development, 1996 (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - Tourism Planning: A New Tool for Reclaiming the Industrial City, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - Tourism Task Force for Greater Cincinnati 1986 Report (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Tourism Task Force for Greater Cincinnati 1986 Report (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Tourism: The Art and the City: A Design Strategy, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Transnational Corporation and Tourism Issues, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Travel Review Conference Proceedings, 4th Annual, 1990 (Box 143, Folder 5)
- Series 8: Photographs, 1970s-2010s; (19 boxes)
  Series 8 consists of photogaphs that document the activities of Partners from the 1970s through 2010s. Subjects include events hosted by Partners, images of commuity activities in cities, and pictures of the Partners staff.
  - Rattley, Jessie, 1953 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Reigeluth, George A., 1970s (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Reilly, William, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Rifkind, Carole, 1975 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Riley, Joseph P., 1970s (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Rouse, James, 1970s (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Royer, Charles, 1980 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Rueda, Ramon, 1970s (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Satterwaite, Ann, 1970s (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - Savas, Emmanuel S., 1981 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Schaeffer, William Donald, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Soloman, Jay, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Southern, Kathy Dwyer, 1998 (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Stein, Peter, 1970s (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - Stokvis, Jack, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 15)
  - Towery, E. Carlisle, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 16)
  - Tumler, John, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified, 1980s-1990s (Box 158, Folder 18)
  - Whyte, William H., 1981 (Box 158, Folder 19)
  - Wilder, A. Tappan, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 20)
  - Wines, James, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 21)
  - Winks, Robin, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 22)
  - Wishart, Alfred, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 23)
  - Africa: Third World Environmental Projects, 1970-1981 (Box 158, Folder 24)
  - Alabama: Birmingham model, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 25)
  - Arizona: various shots of Chandler, Tuscon, and Phoenix, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 26)
  - Australia: Melbourne summer street party, 1985 (Box 158, Folder 27)
  - Australia: Sydney - play equipment, 1982 (Box 158, Folder 28)
  - California: Costa Mesa, 1984 (Box 158, Folder 29)
  - California: Los Angelos, 1993 (Box 158, Folder 30)
  - California: Los Angelos - model of the Museum of Contemporary Art, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 31)
  - California: Los Angelos - music center, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 32)
  - California: Marin County headlands, 1970s (Box 158, Folder 33)
  - California: Napa Valley, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 34)
  - California: Oakland - downtown BART station, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 35)
  - California: San Cruz, 1990s (Box 158, Folder 36)
  - California: San Diego, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 37)
  - California: San Diego Transit System, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 38)
  - California: San Francisco and the Bay Area, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 39)
  - California: San Francisco transit, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 40)
  - California: San Juan - Capistrano Library, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 41)
  - California: various pictures, 1982-1985 (Box 158, Folder 42)
  - California: Venice, 1981 (Box 158, Folder 43)
  - Canada: Montreal, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 44)
  - Canada: Montreal - jet boats tour, 1984 (Box 158, Folder 45)
  - Canada: Montreal - office building, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 46)
  - Canada: Vancouer - Granville Island, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 47)
  - Canada: Vancouver - historical pictures, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 48)
  - Canada: Vancouver - statues, 1980s (Box 158, Folder 49)
  - Florida: Jacksonville, 1980-1986 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Florida: Orlando - "City of Light" logo and article, 1980s (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Florida: St. Petersburg, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Florida: Tampa, 1980s (Box 159, Folder 4)
    Folder 1 of 2
  - Florida: Tampa, 1984-1989 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    Folder 2 of 2
  - Florida: various pictures, 1982 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - France: Paris - city planning, 1980s (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Georgia: Savannah, 1984 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Georgia: various pictures, 1986-1989 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Illinois: Chicago, 1984-1987 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Illinois: Dixon & Tampico - Ronald Reagan's childhood home, 1980s (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Illinois: Lockport, 1980s (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Illinois: various pictures, 1980s (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - India, 1982 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Indiana: Fort Wayne, 1983-1986 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - New Jersey and Virginia, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Minnesota: St. Paul, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Utah: Salt Lake City, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - United Kingdom: England, 1989 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh - zoo, 1984 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Washington, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Washington, 1985 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - New York, 1982 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Minnesota: St. Paul, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Virginia: Alexandria, 1982 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania, 1985 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - Minnesota: Minneapolis - Guthrie Theater, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - Ohio, 1980 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Minnesota: Saint Paul - sign, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - various locations, 1981 (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - New York: convention, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - New York: New York City - Times Square, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 17)
  - New York: New York City, 1982 (Box 160, Folder 18)
  - Europe: United Kingdom - artifacts from the Museum of London, 1982 (Box 160, Folder 19)
  - Virginia: Charlottesville - archeological dig site, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 20)
  - New York: New York City - Green Market, 1976-1979 (Box 160, Folder 21)
  - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 22)
  - New York: New York City - view of skyline, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 23)
  - New York: New York City - important buildings, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 24)
  - New York: New York City, 1980s (Box 160, Folder 25)
  - Maryland: Rockville - demolition of Woolworth Building, 1982 (Box 160, Folder 26)
  - Washington: Seattle - festival, 1980 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Virginia: Rosslyn, 1980s (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Rally Awards in San Diego, 1988 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - National Geographic article "Gulf Coast Oystermen", 1987 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - National Geographic article "Tenacious as Debt, Johnsongrass", 1986 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Lizard, 1980s (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - National Geographic article "To Be Disabled", 1986 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - National Geographic article "Newfoundland and Labrador", 1986 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - maps and artwork from New Amsterdam, 1980s (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Freedman's Villiage black settlement in Arlington, Virginia, 1980s (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Historic Boston, 1980s (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Designs for "Brace-a-bike" and "History Tubes", 1982 (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - National Geographic article "Capital Cities Errect Barriers to Cope to Terrorism Fears", 1987 (Box 161, Folder 13)
  - Open Air project with NOAA, 1980s (Box 161, Folder 14)
  - Public Art, 1978 (Box 161, Folder 15)
  - Urban planning packet, 1982 (Box 161, Folder 16)
  - National Geographic article "Mounties of Today Get Their Men But Not The Stuff of Legend", 1986 (Box 161, Folder 17)
  - National Geographic articles about prehistoric creatures, 1986 (Box 161, Folder 18)
  - Various Partners Board members, 1980s (Box 161, Folder 19)
  - Interactive cultural activities, 1980s (Box 161, Folder 20)
  - South Carolina: structures, 1980s (Box 161, Folder 21)
  - Tennessee: Knoxville - World's Fair, 1982 (Box 161, Folder 22)
  - Tennessee: Chattanooga, 1985 (Box 161, Folder 23)
  - Tennessee: Shelby County - Headstart Program, 1980s (Box 161, Folder 24)
  - Tennessee: Memphis, 1982-1984 (Box 161, Folder 25)
  - Texas: San Antonio, 1981 (Box 161, Folder 26)
  - Texas: Galveston, 1982-1984 (Box 161, Folder 27)
  - Texas, 1914-1986 (Box 161, Folder 28)
  - Annual meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified meetings and events, 1980s-1990s (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Aerial views and landscapes of various cities, 1980s (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Baltimore, Maryland, 1979-1982 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Photograph collections for publications and 3.5" floppy disk, 1989 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Pittsburg, 1984 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Exemplary project photographs and documentation, 1980s (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Photograph system media library inventory, 1980s (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Resources for Livability Magazine, 1981-1992 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Resources for Livability Magazine, 1972-1981 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Board Members, 1986-1987 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Nature, 1980s (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Public Art, 1982-1984 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Public Art, 1980-1984 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - unidentified pictures, 1980s (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - pictures for PLACE magazine, 1987-1988 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - unidentified pictures, 1980s (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Rhode Island, 1980s (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Planning Team, 1980s-1990s (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified event, 1980s (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Art in Public Places, 1970s-1980s (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Art in Public Places, 1973-1984 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - State of the American Community, 1993-1994 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    Folder 1 of 3
  - State of the American Community, 1994 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    Folder 2 of 3
  - State of the American Community, 1988-1992 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    Folder 3 of 3
  - Unidentified, 1970s-1980s (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - uUnidentified, 1980s-1990s (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - A Celebration of Vision and Community Spirit, 38777 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - A Celebration of Vision and Community Spirit, 39508 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - African American Tourism Forum, 1980s (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - America's Most Livable Places Awards, 1986 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Annecy, France Conference, 1997 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Annual Meeting I, 1978 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting II, 1979 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting III, 1980 (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - Annual Meeting IV, 1981 (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting V, 1982 (Box 166, Folder 10)
  - Arts Edge Conference, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1981 (Box 166, Folder 11)
  - Asian Pacific islander Americans: An Asset for America's Future, 2000s (Box 166, Folder 12)
  - Board Meeting at Meridian House, 1979 (Box 166, Folder 13)
  - Bowers Museum in Santa Ana, California, 1980s (Box 166, Folder 14)
  - Bridge Builders, 38139 (Box 166, Folder 15)
  - Bridge Builders, 38687 (Box 166, Folder 16)
  - Bridge Builders, April, 2008 (Box 166, Folder 17)
  - Chattanooga Workshop, 1980 (Box 166, Folder 18)
  - Hispanics in the U.S. Conference, 1980s (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Cities Tour, 1980s (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Interns Meeting of NEA, late 1970s (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Kingstort Goal Setting Forum, 1980s (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Liverpool Forum, 1989 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Lowell Forum - "Industrial Cities in Transition", 1984 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - McNulty Presentation to Mexico Delegation, 1990s (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Most Livable Community Awards, 1994 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Most Livable Community Awards, 1994 (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - Museums Conference, 1990s (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - National Leadership Forum, 1994 (Box 167, Folder 11)
  - NLC Reception, 1980s (Box 167, Folder 12)
  - Oakland Public Art Workshop, 30225 (Box 167, Folder 13)
  - Opening Forum and Luncheon, 1980s (Box 167, Folder 14)
  - Partners Council National Recognition Program, 1983 (Box 167, Folder 15)
  - Partners for Livable Communites Awards, 1996 (Box 167, Folder 16)
  - Partners for Livable Communites Awards, 1997 (Box 167, Folder 17)
  - PLC 20th Annual Awards, 1997 (Box 167, Folder 18)
  - Glendening, P.N., 1990s (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Green, Alan, 1980s (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Hampton, Lionel, 1982 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Handler, Sheryl, 1980s (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Hanks, Nancy, 1970s-1990s (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Hodsell, Frank, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Hudnut, William, 1980s-1990s (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - Jackson, Maynard, 1980s (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Jacobson, Dori, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Huey, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1970s-1980s (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - Jones, Pat, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 12)
  - Kahan, Richard, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 13)
  - Kaptur, Mary, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 14)
  - Keefe, Frank, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 15)
  - Kent, Fred, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 16)
  - Keune, Russell, 1980s (Box 168, Folder 17)
  - Knight, Roy, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 18)
  - Kramer, Lawrence F., 1970s (Box 168, Folder 19)
  - Krauss, John, 1980s (Box 168, Folder 20)
  - Landingham, Van, 1990s (Box 168, Folder 21)
  - Landrieu, Moon, 1980s (Box 168, Folder 22)
  - Latimer, George, 1990s (Box 168, Folder 23)
  - Lazarus, Fred, IV, 1980s (Box 168, Folder 24)
  - Lu, Weiming, 1980s (Box 168, Folder 25)
  - Maier, Henry, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 26)
  - Malt, Hal, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 27)
  - Marsh, Henry, 1980s-1990s (Box 168, Folder 28)
  - Massoni, Al, 1980s (Box 168, Folder 29)
  - Matthias, Charles, 1980s (Box 168, Folder 30)
  - McLaughlin, Stephen, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 31)
  - McNulty, Bob, 1980s-1990s (Box 168, Folder 32)
  - Means, Mary, 1983 (Box 168, Folder 33)
  - Melillo, Joseph V., 1980s (Box 168, Folder 34)
  - Mitman, Philip, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 35)
  - Morris, William, 1970s (Box 168, Folder 36)
  - Moulinier, Jacques, 1993 (Box 168, Folder 37)
  - Notter, George M., 1980s (Box 168, Folder 38)
  - O'Leary, John J., 1970s (Box 168, Folder 39)
  - Ostergard, Paul, 1980s (Box 168, Folder 40)
  - People of Patners Directory Photos, 1970s-1980s (Box 168, Folder 41)
  - Pierce, Neal, 1990s (Box 168, Folder 42)
  - Pines, Marion, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 43)
  - Pittas, Micheal, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 44)
  - PLC Staff, 1980s-1990s (Box 168, Folder 45)
  - PLC Staff, 1980s-1990s (Box 168, Folder 46)
  - Canada: Vancouver - various pictures, 1980s-1990s (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Colorado: Denver, 1980s (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut: Danbury, 1980s (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut: Hartford, 1980s (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut: New Haven, 1970s (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - District of Columbia: Dupont Circle, 1989 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - District of Columbia: East Building Project for the National Gallery, 1970s (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - District of Columbia: exhibition on Animals, 1980s (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - District of Columbia: Georgetown, 1980s (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - District of Columbia: Old Post Office, 1980s-1990s (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - District of Columbia: various pictures, 1980s (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - District of Columbia: Vietnam Memorial, 1980s (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - Europe: Partners for Livable Communites, 1980s-1990s (Box 169, Folder 13)
  - Europe: Partners for Livable Communites, 1980s-1990s (Box 169, Folder 14)
  - Indiana: Indianapolis, 1982-1984 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Indiana: New Harmony, 1970s (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - International: various pictures, 1980s (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - International: various pictures, 1980s (Box 170, Folder 4)
    Folder 2 of2
  - Iowa, 1980s (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Kentucky: Louisville, 1980s (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Kenya: Nairobi, 1986 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Louisana: New Orleans, 1983 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Maine: Portland, 1984 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Maine: Portland, 1980s (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Maryland: Baltimore, 1980s (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified event, 1984 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Finding aid, undated (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - New York, 1984 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - New York, 1982 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Texas: Houston - The Galleria, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Texas: Best (James Wines), 1972-1979 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Oregon, 1982 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Texas: Austin, 1984 (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - Washington, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - Minnesota, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - Virginia: Alexandria, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - New Mexico: Albuquerque, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 12)
  - New Jersey, 1983 (Box 171, Folder 13)
  - Virginia: Richmond, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 14)
  - Massachussetts: Salem, 1970s (Box 171, Folder 15)
  - Virginia: Orange, 1984 (Box 171, Folder 16)
  - New York: Troy, 1977-1978 (Box 171, Folder 17)
  - Pennsylvania: Easton, 1970s (Box 171, Folder 18)
  - Texas: Galveston, 1982 (Box 171, Folder 19)
  - Tennessee: Memphis, 1970s (Box 171, Folder 20)
  - New York: New York City, 1970s (Box 171, Folder 21)
  - Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh, 1984 (Box 171, Folder 22)
  - Minnesota: Minneapolis, 1970s (Box 171, Folder 23)
  - New York, 1983 (Box 171, Folder 24)
  - Massachussetts: Boston, 1982 (Box 171, Folder 25)
  - New Jersey, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 26)
  - Minnesota, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 27)
  - New Jersey: Mount Laurel, 1983 (Box 171, Folder 28)
  - Virginia: Richmond, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 29)
  - Michigan: Grand Rapids, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 30)
  - Washington: Seattle, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 31)
  - Vermont, 1980s (Box 171, Folder 32)